Inventory of the Gordon Leo McDonough papers 0366
USC Libraries Special Collections
- SUPPLEMENT listing of materials in FILING CABINET
  - Election, 1952
  - Election, 1954
  - Election, 1956
  - Complete rendu de la I Conference [UNK] tenue a Bruxeeles, 14 au 22 September 1961 (Draw Draw 3)
  - Los Angeles Calif. City blocks (US census of Housing, 1960
  - Los Angels, Calif. by census tracts block, 1960
  - FOLDER A Fifty'thr Interparliamentary Union Brussels Belgium Ostend Belgium, LonDon, England, Paris, Berlin West East Hamburg jewry, 1961, Sept 14-22 Sept 15/17
  - FOLDER B Gordon Mc Donough (water damaged)
  - FOLDER C Reference materials expenses receipts for expenditures. Trip to Europe, Aug.2-Oct.4 1959
    Folders A B C contain materials suchas f i.: Autoclub of Toscany's guides Maps,booklets f.i.Berlin Facts Figures,France Facts Figures,guidebooks Florence Heidelberg, museums monuments of Rom, Vatica, Louvre museum foto's, Rome booklets guide.
  - Aldine's (Draw Draw 4)
  - Bell Reception
  - Bishop
  - Contracts cheek request forms
  - Democrats for [UNK] Donough
  - Demo-list
  - Speeches
  - Sponsors democrats -Petty
  - Truman Marine Corps letters, (4 folio's)